Regarding the antiquities of the
state, so I teach the steps on
the path.
The plan is City News,
and this is a 15-year plan.
No, not
15,
not 50. His wife
and eight years have already had the
menu item to begin the body, but
many people aren't there from the beginning,
such a review,
and that's why I repeat the
previous years
every day. Every day
I make a little more progress. In the evening,
the printout comes out,
and then you can also
learn better in the EU what has already been covered. In the
evening, I mainly do the
review, so the
review of what has already been covered
in the old classes.
The first page has a hard dog on it,
and on the next page, there's a
car salesman
who sells the couple a tissue.
And how I best do the
review after each year
is that I use these pictures
because pictures are easier to
remember.
I call the idea-based approach; these are,
so to speak, idea pictures.
Then you should be able to remember it more easily. In addition,
we will also determine and also have pictures for the new material.
Then you can test your own understanding.
Just cover the writing
and then look at the
pictures
and try to
remember the meaning.
Tonight
I'll teach you the meaning of the first
six pictures
from the last few years,
because star the tumor. And tomorrow, where I myself won't be,
we'll have a trophy.
I'll put a name
on the student list
and then I'll give you a microphone.
Then you'll have the opportunity
to prove yourself, since the beavers are in front of all
these people.
So, team, tomorrow I need to have some kind of
list where I can choose people. So
if he wanted to have his name removed from the list, he
gives the data for $100.
Then maybe take that name from
the list
and you get 50 and I get 15.
That's a real deal. Okay, it
's the right number. So, the number of
the first picture. In
other words, we have 108.
I started this repeat from
last year. So,
if you want the first 108,
we can give you the document online.
Can you do that?  First 180,
okay, is that possible,
or is it also better on the knowledge base? This,
of course, shows rank
1. So I'll start now with 109.
So this guy sells the couple a
car,
and in English, we say, so to speak, a
used car dealer, and it has a
slightly negative connotation.
Yes, he said, "Musk, on this car,
the last owner was 80 years old.
She used the car once a month." Then they talk a
lot,
then they buy the car,
and then the next week,
that's what you call a used car dealer. So they can
talk well, and then they
buy the car,
and in English, we say, "That's
a good salesman, please," and
sales pitch
here. And why did I put the picture
here now? In the
business edition, in this long
tradition,
the steps on the way,
1000 years,
all the diamonds, all together
in one book.
We would, of
course, have these texts in
many
countries. We created the catalog.
[Music]
320,000 books.
We have 320,000 books.  Found
Mongolian
Russia
India
we have all these books
and now
I suppose that will take five generations
which is simply
it is, so to speak, all these books
summarized into one whole and that is then
called a lamp on the
way and studying what you do you do you don't have to
think much just one
step at a time, one step at a time, it
was already fun here if you
limit the class here
and if you come every year Macsteel
next year elections
super stage in front of super beautiful
[Music]
yes I was there this year for
us kids my singers in front of friends who
simply
kidnapped me neighbors had an apprenticeship
there
and then I thought
it's even beautiful is 20 Thailand
and then Jasmin agreed then
we're going to Berlin now is here
[Applause]
so here is the citizenship
if I
do so just that Moody's 1
2346 Burg
are finished you don't have to think much about it
come
[Music]
maybe
became
unemployed today is already pretty close or
also creates a  A man goes into the encounter at the
beginning of the lamb
from the car salesman,
so he's back again, says this car is
so beautiful.
Beforehand, just do
1234.
It's a tradition
in Buddhism, it ran
before he even knew anything was right.
Then the teacher has to
sell it to you well, to look
very special, very nice with you, very
special.
There you can see 500 years into the future,
you can know what you'll be doing in 500 years.
Youth present
in the world, in Tunis, you can
see every person in the world in 20 minutes, see all beings in the world,
you can have direct love for all
beings in this world. Seven
billion people in this world,
one after the other, in 20 minutes, cow,
so that colleagues, and that's called
a good thing
at the beginning of Islam, a
teacher has to do that, so that it has to be
a good conversation. This Mannheim
studies, then practice, and we, brothers, you,
then you will soon become a Buddha.
So not just empty talk about Pippo,
first tell people what's
really cool there.  traded and then they'll get
really hungry, that's this, that's what
we do, yes, brings, yes,
now I have to learn something, now I had to learn something,
why did he, listen to this now, my
team
has me at
my long empty job, it's already
half finished, I have about
six more years, that is, yes, and then it is
your task, company, to
continue this, the next
generation of Heart of the Dance grows, to avoid,
I don't have to do the dance tonight, I've already
done that, I've already passed that on to
the next
generation, okay, yes,
you're next,
he learned, people, who are you, tell people why that's
so cool, that was cool now, is that,
here begins to meditate, there does this and that and that,
business class comes,
a bit
boring, to others, since the speaker
[music],
we do business
and then we would be these shells, denial
and imitation, but I don't want
any migration, learn, for example,
in Russia, I
'm not even Buddhist,
coast, I'm a circle,
I just
want to do business,
why should I, then, now, where he had
Hermann Schneider, learn or
meditation,
if the businessman to  Inheritance technology
meditation with
meditation, they work with factory teams. New
product, then you can already
see next year's product this year.
Then they can already see
next year's iPhone this year. For example, in
pictures, 15 could be insane, because you could
see which stocks will go up
this year for next year.
If you meditate regularly,
you have to have a good
sales pitch here, especially from
business people. Not to meditate,
but do you understand?
If you do the therapy with strong [unclear] every day,
then you already know
this year which stocks will go up next year.
Maybe hear about it.
So you have to buy this
and sell the meditation, that it's
a Buddhist tradition to
really stimulate the students.
Someone, it does
n't come to your program, there are
so many ideas and so
[music],
but I just want to use my heart. I do
n't want to take steps from Dr. [unclear],
this whole majority. I want to
use my heart,
and in this tradition
you can't open your heart without
your mind.
Here comes the understanding. First
is the understanding of  Without
understanding the pen,
you can't open your heart.
Yes, so about the sea, if someone
screams at you at home, then
you feel angry at the historical one, and
after you've studied it, or let's say
before we have stability,
then you're angry at the one who
screams. The study, the
pills, but after the dictionary, the
first
fan, you're angry then.
You can't
really love your husband without the pieces presented by the
minister. You can't
really love other people if he doesn't just use the pen.
Typical in this tradition,
you can't live
because
if you don't understand who made it,
he's in the picture. I, in this
tradition, think
we only take it. We think
that to open hearts and think
to open the heart
when we understand that the
members represent.
If you think that the man
is an angry person, then you will
never have a perfect marriage. It wasn't even
possible.
Then you will only have, so to speak, a
peace
in battle, a
truce.
Because wood is
finally understanding who
then it is impossible to have a
happy marriage.  Having a happy
marriage is the goal, because it's
the most beautiful goal in
this world. If you do
n't understand where the man comes from,
then that's impossible.
An assumption of mine, and that's why I
need your help.
So, I've been with my
husband
in China for 30 years. Should the woman follow the Quran? I
understand. I didn't even look at it.
I like it
for my wife, and I
like to take on this responsibility.
But
in the spring, Cookie is from the 11th. But
during the 30 years that I've been here for my
husband, it's
not simply washed away. Is there some way
that
I can give them this seed of
system change? Then
I
want to dig up the water,
and then I should
find a strange partner,
and then I'll give my acquaintance a
lot to admire at home, and
then I've found a method with lots of coffee. So, I've found the step-by-step method.
Next year, I'll be back very
slowly, contouring their house. Then
Kessler says, "Come to my house for dinner,
I have to show you something,"
and then I went to their house, a
very beautiful house.
I won't show you the city.  say
because you will then the people will be
a huge table
she said additionally and there was
nothing on the table yet
only a small bell
and then she rang the bell
Europa and then against the Greeks door open
and come then her husband came out
here
he had a lady's apron on the aids
then because he is so popular generally
the food is ready and only here no not yet
hope you do it right now
then she had me
what happened
yes I taught myself how he plays out this event the more precisely to say that
I managed that in two months
[Music]
two months made the progress
and then he started the
better team and then I thought why should
I stop there
I thought I can do these
steps too no miracle butter
boil and
now also the setup thing no argument
is cook a discussion
she didn't ask him not asked
to cook she didn't
ask him to wash the dishes hardly shoots
because he comes from her seed am youth had
you here have you full  Justice,
because the man has to follow your names.
I can say yes, just be full of
love, just
be in front, say
I love you.
Can you please do the dishes? Man, the man
from mills, where, and then the war goes on,
but
in this system, then the man of the
city, he comes from the
post office, change that, and then
the customer will,
so tomorrow, tomorrow evening,
he already has after 9, after this class,
there will be a very special class,
could come back then, at the cost of
Madonna and the left, no normal computer comes,
and then I ask for the men, and
why can I never, he wanted to play
[Applause]
now even deeper, let's
go a little deeper, even in the Star
Movie Channel, have you seen the movie Titanic?
Yes, so there, the purpose is to
shovel, that was the biggest ship in the
world, the USA, and that was brand new, first
time religious, that was the first time
that it was ever used, highest tones
come, and here comes the Titanic,
because here is, and here is the iceberg,
mountain white, so a mountain of a
chip card, and when the ship crashes into the
iceberg,
it is a huge  The problem is,
he understands differently, that the iceberg is what
the expert sees live, the seeds are in the mind of the
woman, the technology is that she has the sky
and the Titanic, these are the seeds in the
man's grasp, the iceberg means one
hates her, do what is necessary,
and here is the man who has the
seeds, and
here is the woman who has the seeds,
that he lets this happen, plays it out, and now
who will win now? The house in Street
View grows together, that one sees the
built-in one, which is that it will be stronger here now,
but no one, the business will always
bend, both, that can't be, do
you have a piece,
okay, you have, you will, someone has to do
the dishes,
impossible,
so the man has the lawn,
light test, to do the dishes,
and the woman also has the seeds, are
n't we to do the dishes,
she has to do it, probably
the guests will invite,
either the woman's seeds have to
be stronger, or that one stands there,
the
bus messenger,
broken beats, and both can be true,
in the church today, in the man's kitchen,
legally she was only you,
the woman washes the chili  and did the
washing up before that and in the woman's kitchen
the man does the washing up is indeed
capitals and how can two kitchens be in
one kitchen
should stand the ok
stands the
can the pen one can also be a
woman toy small components
I am now doing with the matter
the first is finished is in this
system
true love
has understanding
I love my husband and
I am working on my name and therefore
improved
and the man also improves the woman
and
then there is harmony in the kitchen in the
basement or art knows no
love without majority but
thinking about so in the display it is
on this way it means newcomer is a
couple
who is so full of understanding is the way
through the instructions learn bdp in the
right believes
news then it should also be used for days
is Buddhist that is Buddhism that
is our tradition first learn
and then used at home
and that was now my
sales pitch she
never does the washing up
okay
my body started here I
cut off my finger and opened it
because I also still
I made a big mistake and
who holds someone clear is I put them in
my  Class invited
the second
time
such a small light
[Music] there are
many things you can learn, like, for example, have you
learned the pen, Mio, I
need another pen now
because
advertising for a pen
before he came here,
my class, did you think it's just a
stable built and don't even think about
what I can do, it comes from me
now, they can come from Penn, does it
come from the pen now,
someone asks, does the horse come from you
or does it come from the pen, the
ZDK
Christa say that I don't care, it's simply, it's simply
irrelevant, it comes from here,
comes from me, okay, you go and then
you start, then that at Juve, so if you
find out where the substance comes from,
you always have to do the dishes, oh
yeah, he the pen, then YouTube Opel,
and then he explains to someone, Steffi,
and before we, the pen class, there are
no fees, then there is a
certain darkness of the pen comfort and
the pen now comes,
then someone teaches you about the dog and
the writing consumption and then a
light dawns in your mind, June in  The
darkness into the clock, so there are
billions of darknesses in the world,
so there are billions of things he does
n't notice,
but now one of the film became
light
[Music]
in Buddhism with
teachers, like everywhere else, turning on lights,
handed out, right, right, not, because
then I can do it. In the encounter at the
beginning of the film, Agnes, at the beginning,
the darkness is over the open-pit mine, a little
disco, no art, you were taught that in school,
but then you can't avoid
coming, and this darkness then becomes
light, came, share,
then to Thailand, Thailand
has arrived, and every time, 0, 1, it
always goes out again, a new light goes
out, in which you always go out again, new lights go out,
and that's the first time, that's
the meaning of this picture,
next picture,
100 dollars,
it's the teacher, mustn't arrive, this
picture has
[Music]
the greatest portable wealth
[Music], do
you have a microphone?
[Music]
If you give the wrong answer now, do
you have to give dollars? You can't
do a little bit of business here.
[Music] [
Music]
Things
like, seriously, the answer should have two parts,
twice 50 dollars
[Music]
Can you repeat the question?
This picture shows
the greatest
wealth,
so portable is very strict.
That might still be entered.
Tesla isn't so portable, it's
just too heavy.
It continues
[Music]
If the answer is as long as it's
usually wrong
[Music]
That's like when the accountant said
that you should best put the healthy
YouTube in further insurance
instead of another person's Sondheims in the mountains.
Sometimes you should also ask in the back.
In Germany,
the first part comes
from us, moment by moment.
If you make this answer, then
you can become these teachers,
little in the costs are
[Music]
This
OK Germany type, two parts
[Music]
The accumulation of merit and
wisdom,
we think that we
think that
the multi-material i tity in all
existing things, and the second, you
can share this knowledge with everyone,
and that will then be the greatest wealth in
your pocket.
[Music]
Nothing about this,
therefore
[Music]
The
whirlwind in the negative.
I'm telling you,
I was a few evenings ago with my
Friends in a very nice
restaurant, far away,
on the left and right sides
a toilet. These pictures are supposed to be in them, and there
's a big sign above it: Men's
Toilet. The
debators and
under the signs,
men have to go to the left.
Although he was always right, he fought
the battles. His wife gave him
pretty good answers,
but not exactly.
What you learn here in this class,
you can take anywhere. This is what's up
here. If there's a war
tomorrow, so
if she loses her house and your house,
Beckham, and you
couldn't go home again, in parts,
so to speak, for the rest of your life in
Thailand, then you've lost everything: a
car, if at home from the bank account,
family, resounding class, you can Davos.
But what you learn in this class here,
you can never lose.
No one can take this from you. This is
a
hobby, this is the only safe one, the only
safe one. You can
keep it. Toucan copy. So learn things
that could hold you up here, could help you,
because the bank account, of course, can go bankrupt.
A country can also break down
and go bankrupt. It can
also lose this, but then you lose this
No one can take away the idea
that they always have,
that's definitely parrying here, and
the second part of the answer is
youth equity,
and that's the only thing you
can take with you,
not your body or your family.
You can't even take your own
name,
but these ideas had to become them
by staying that way, the 12, so it's
enough, that's as valuable as diamonds,
postage and very portable, taking it with you, there is, even if it can
destroy the whole world, it
's still, even
if you can, you can also do it with your
heart, well, that's a good answer,
okay?
[Music] If you
want to have a novel blessed, then you can do it up
here.  I
could do that every day
[music]
ok
appointments
is the next showing
so now the next 112
be English there is
a concert film is
English language turn it comes from
a piece by Shakespeare or Goethe
from Sony Germany
so it is someone who wants so to speak
that is the drunken pinto the icon
goes for you and then this
powerful person said I can give you sometime
but I need a so to speak used to
your company carbon fund from your
meat
here I can have white give would
here I have extra so
give me now
and then he can so to speak get the
success for the rest of his life
and there is the story behind that
the run crazy a lot going on Tokyo Pieper
made namely liked to kill people and
CS
and he lived in a cage
children please he
kidnapped people and then ate them
the piano bar
and the people already knew them 2000
users and is about 2000 years ago in
India
and if you the damage you are
simply change prof who very very
thin
and then there was a prince and he had
a very pure heart and
one day
saw
all this at the palace in politics
and he wanted to take two or three people with him,
the award Prince Philip, there was
the prince with the pure heart
and he studied lamps in the
palace
and then it came to pass and took two
or three people with exactly artificial and
then Gryslow said he had
no fear, he said
if someone looked
quite appetizing
and then he took him to
his cave,
then the case started, they sat down
and made the bay hunter and then
the prince started to cry, that's how it will be,
you should actually be the
prince of this country, used to be
brave, actually you should
be brave, New York
and now 21, therefore they can, that
the dying,
listed weeks, will be, said Franz,
we both are you, then do you
think I'm
not afraid of the 1,
you took me away from my Lambert class,
I had no opportunity, also
guidelines for the teachers  Tours
offer to get me away from it
and now I will
then I have no opportunity to
de/tank my teachers I wanted to
my teachers may the prince
then said the prince
prince on the monster said to the monster
[Music]
let me just go away for half an hour
I'll go back to the palace then thinks means
I have to my teachers there
[Music]
we only taught one poem
and then I don't have to go now and
then I would like to
say goodbye there I would like to thank you then
I'll come back then it can eat me
says that was
stupid and
there the transfer became the shortest they like I
have
I respect I don't want to continue like this
I will stand for a year
Thuringia piu
that people and
I am not like I keep my
promise
and then says that one went there before his father
yesterday
and then says the tanks rode out on the horse
why hunting
he also sounds like that he
said oh so your father who gives tips on
what they are so good at and then that's good no no
and
I  Kill too, what is the big
difference now, Presley with the trends
and the king, he is diligent, first
you are just like me, the Prince, the prince, no, no,
you are, why
Pippo is like that, people,
that is worse than
the monster office,
I am now curious about your
comeback, whether you will come back,
I don't think you will come back,
the fire between
[music]
back, but thanks your teacher and says goodbye,
and I
think that
is a very famous victim,
he had 1000,
he had 1000 gold coins for each,
for each line, 10,000 pieces of gold,
teacher, excuse me, I don't have to,
market comes, I will not come back, I promised
to go back, the
barbecue
grill festival,
why does the father say, followed and has the
keeper, you must, ca
n't keep his promise to him, will
you be the king if you are a
good politician behind Bismarck, and if
I have to, my child, have you make up the
promised, a youth announces, if he
makes a promise, the promise that
Not good, then you can change that
from Newron, the cantons. How can you ever
lead a country if you're so
honest?
And then the prince says, and that's no good king, a
good king keeps his
word.
[Music]
Eventim Monster himself, a monster
opposite the king, and tipped over, the king will keep
his word. Well, because here in Bern, and
then he went back,
and then the monster says, weapons trades are
coming, a fries pizza fries, I already
said
that I know that you'll keep to it, you're
strange. In the prince's return, the
cook with, so okay, says the 20 hp ready, quite
cheaper for me now somehow, and
then the monster was mostly, this is
my house,
I decide when I eat,
I will decide when I cook you. What do they teach you that you go back there, what did they teach you, a
very special club brought you, that's
also teaching me
what some bölw the meaning of the
verse, even if you have to
crash, even if you cut your meat,
if you have to
pay for meat for a line, then it's worth it,
and then the monster has, so to speak,
taken the material, has
it  On the red, he suffered, bowed
before the prince,
okay, teach me, you are a good teacher.
Then he started learning
art back then,
and later he saw that the teachers would have seen it
directly. It's a cool
story
in Linz. It was true,
it means that it's very
valuable, that there is something very different for
tomorrow. The consequence is that
if you pay a lot of money for the plane
to Hawaii, pay
or not,
it's worth it. Do
n't hesitate. There are
people who cut off their arms. He
ran for 17 years
and received this lesson.
Seventeen out of
you had 17 hours
or three hours of flight, which results in
costs of 14 hours, with two
more hours of heart. It can't even be as
bad as now at
home.
So I don't know, but I now have three
starters, and how now 113,
that's the picture with the dog. This
okay,
that is now the relationship
between the teacher and students.
It should look like this
in the long tables, in the tradition. There is a kind of
false respect. The
student is always  I heard such a teacher, I have thought of
my teacher for 30 years,
then I was already then I washed
his laundry,
heaven of studies, so I have
seen hundreds of students,
caution would come
[music]
that with
this kind of student
teacher,
what are you doing here, worry, I have experienced many, many
such students,
then I have experienced the others,
llama, could the teacher come, wine,
then say soon, a little,
maybe,
then they make a beautiful t,
thank you very much for making me so cool now, so much
fun, that's great, super, your
class is so much fun, makes me
totally happy,
and then it's a little like the
teacher had a favorite dog,
I like you,
yes, in English we call that,
allowed, affection, loving, for love, hurt, inclination,
and that is
different than respect,
can sometimes be a little artificial, affection
and love,
I have had so much fun again, that
my husband is so much better,
maybe yes,
40 years here, my favorite front,
that's a different feeling,
supposed to think, the title is brother,
one must of course think that the
teacher a modern so the Buddha came
disadvantage
and you should respect him we the
Buddha
but there are two kinds
one is respect for and
then you make everyone else nervous
car work and
respect
she is my personal assistant for
25 years
we
really have respect for each other so
I will now drink the hot
chocolate
all love you no chocolate are
they gone from me Willi
brother Luc tomorrow can must
namely make clear is a brother long
lives a life has no chocolate
title
you are you must respect me no
that is lovingly caring I love
you I want you to stay feels
different
that is affection
that is a kind of love
it is better than respect
it is a higher form of respect just
expects me like a
and
scales away make Ludger Kramer must
now get out of the lama okay okay okay
so I just sat down
that the loving
and that is a true long student back then
is so cool
[Music]
we
have we a
whole lineage I don't know
who I am I guess I am just a
loss  Because I'm before you, you'll be
students for another 40 years, later, in
about 1000 years,
you'll be the next teachers
and have fun with it. It's
not very cold, I don't want to be
so full of respect.
We're more so-called, and that's
okay. The harbor
is the fun line,
head, be really close, though.
The spirit is incredibly far away. They create
the skies,
but the behavior
is very far away.
Okay, the major shareholder, hump, yes, that's what it's about.
We are Sharon Jarvis, there will be an
appointment, it's too close to our
family tradition, and 1000 is for the
last thousand years. It's friendly,
happy, full of fun.
[Music]
Correct,
2000 castles, 2000 books, quite
cheap, but the feeling
in hand,
he stands, that's how it is. Respect is
true respect, that's how affection is.
Let's have another pretty one, and then
we'll do questions and answers. That's
Alaska Bauer, that's the last half
hour, it's free, and the pico, that's for
you. So if you take everything out of hand,
then you'd have to be a family,
simply
fantastic.  Just ask and answer, I think I'll find them,
but I have to take a picture now. You
can have three cups today,
300 hot minute, as I've taught it often.
This would be Steve, she had her
evening up first,
but he's a teacher,
brand of 4, 1 million of
pens for Steve,
Mandala,
Claire Lee
in the Federal Office,
so something good.
[Music]
A good student shouldn't be like three
cups. Okay, my husband was July first. First,
you can't mix different
teachers together.
Second, you
should be open to teachers
and not stand on your head.
And then
you shouldn't think, don't drip, don't leak.
I say
yes.
[Applause]
Okay, at
So now we have six different ones.
They had the car sale, Heidmark. We had
the light, had the portable
setting.
You can go, and even
cutting yourself is worth it. She often has a
child there. Then we had dog affection,
Steve's jersey. Then we had Steve's
three cups.
Have the novelty for the morning? You  You need to
know tomorrow evening, okay? I'll take my
leave then. I'll choose a name,
Judith, brand of. Then you'll
get the microphone.
That's the wrong answer
in
any questions.
Tiebreak or tee,
or maybe he secretly wanted to
go home. WorldCom, then you
could do that.
We have about 20 minutes left.
[Music]
Thank you so much for coming to our teachings.
I have questions related to
death.
When I see a person in front of me, so
I see you.
[Music]
The two things I can do in my mind are:
first,
I can
tell the person
that I can do this death meditation, this
kind of technique, and second,
that people can remember
what good things they did
in life.
These two things... What else
can I do?
What else can I do to help the person
in this difficult
situation? If they die a few
hours later,
how can I help the person
if they haven't had any training
to experience a higher birth?
He's a goal machine.
[Music]
She should
Here's a chance
to
have,
actually only in that
Chinese as a
good question.
I also asked my teacher this question,
and it has to do with the lineage.
In June, if you were a boy,
then you can say, "I heard this from
my teacher, it's
lineage.
My father was a very tall,
sturdy man,
and of natural years, and he killed
many animals.
He also killed many fish, various
fish. He even had a fishing boat
for fun, kickers from phishing pink, and he took
us along
to catch social fish.
They were small,
about 7
[Music].
Then he taught us how to be a fisherman.
I also killed a deer once. He taught
us how to
stick the kindergartens,
and then he also taught us how to gut the
deer safely
with a special anemometer,
so here,
and then you do it like this on four
groups, then you open that,
isn't that all? You have to gut the
things
[Music].
Then you're full of blood,
gut the wagon,
it's the first time
Then I told my father I
couldn't do it,
and he got really angry.
We grew up in a laid-back cowboy town in
Arizona,
so to speak. It's a tradition where
every young man experiences it. I'm
sorry, but I can't do it.
And then he got cancer,
and then the doctor told me
my father needed a special operation.
We'll start down there, work our way up to the top,
and then we'll take part of his leg
and put this back in.
[Music]
I didn't know anything about it back then,
but it was
exactly the same cut we
used for fish and deer.
And then my father later had a grip. Then
I asked my teacher, "
My father is dying."
I was up here performing operations.
Yes, when the incision is opened, and
then we come in, even if it's
forgotten, they're sewn up again.
You can't help him anymore.
And then I drove there, and for the
last few weeks, I've been with him.
Then I asked my teacher, "
What can I do to help my father?" It
's like you said,
Christian Kost, there is...  Namely, a
very good tradition:
when a person dies,
you call on heaven, say "come, priest,"
and then he comes and asks
everyone to leave.
Then the person is alone with the priest,
and the
priest gathers
those who want to speak about the bad things. It's the same
in the Moselle and in Buddhism
as it is in the media. If you
make a mistake in your life,
if you tell someone,
you hold a clinic, then they help you. This is
very
strong in some places, and I find it helpful to say, "I'm really sorry," and "I won't do that again."
Then they
destroy it. And my teacher
in me said, "With your father, first of all, make sure
he tells you all the
bad things." And then,
secondly,
remind him of the
good things he did. So, "
Father,
you always taught me how to
respect other people,"
and he was a pretty good
businessman.
You taught me to be honest with others.
You taught me to work. Thank you very much for that.
And
he was also very good with children.
We have...  A lot,
and you were always so patient with us,
never hit us, not even
helped them clean up,
and sometimes you just have to outsmart them. He was
n't exactly religious,
went to church when my mother landed in space,
but he didn't like that very much,
and then I thought I had to
somehow get a confession out of him, get him to admit it. He
died, couldn't even eat properly, had become
very thin,
and all he ever did was watch TV.
Then I sat down and watched TV
with him.
So, Father, I remember you said
you were at war,
you told me you killed many people
there. Yes, yes, I killed many people.
Would you do it again?
No. A very nice spot, they
could. And then I just outsmarted him into admitting it,
and then
he was able to clean up the mess.
Then I just talked to him like that, and
you can do it that way too.
And you don't have to say that this is the
religious thing to do, because
when they talk about their bad
deeds,
when they say, "I won't
do it again," then...  Is this seen almost
cleared
and now one last radio station
if a person dies before the
new one
can you 4 49 days
then it is very likely that she
feels now the Bardot for the
users mountain who
typically forget that the
dead aunt means and then they come
into the kitchen
and why is everyone crying I am now Hilde and
no one can the higher senses
and then the women say
and everyone
sees
then they become quite
honest my family why he doesn't go
here questions left 9 and then people so for
the first hour the
series becomes annoying
I have died
49 days stay
and the love
and they want to be at home be on course
and of course they hear what he is
talking about
and that's why it is very good to
talk about what good things my father
my teacher said that bath time
is lottery time
in the council life takes a little money
meanwhile eight nine and ten the
files
at this time you choose the
seed that determines the next life
and that went word very difficult game
and then I have  I asked my teacher
what that means,
I'll tell you tomorrow, that's the ball
for the stay close and title, that's so to speak the
benefit of being so close,
and since I tell you tomorrow, Gander notices the
next day in the evening, the outside,
then he also has a blade,
my llama, so the bell rang,
he is, and whether they are in Gmund, and he was
the abbot, and he had the only
television in the whole place, cowardly for that,
and that was supposedly for that, so the
latest news, but
news gladly heard,
that always means that back then there was real stuff on television, look,
that's the answer to your
question,
yesterday you asked me about this
special one,
namely in the 2,
here it is, removed from Demmin, a bay window,
every evening in
America at the same
time, at 7 o'clock, the TV show, there is
a special television show,
forum, very beautiful woman,
environment minister in a very short
miniskirt, civil chamber, she comes out on
television, it is better, and there is
then a special double,
and she has that on
her hand, and
then she draws the lottery  Number from the
whole country,
20 million people are waiting. My
opinion was that he should draw a number.
That's it, that's it. That it's in Japan,
while in the province of the process,
is present at the train station. The children
there see the person, then the lottery
number 1 in Whistler. Here, the people
they put in the mini-work. With this
life, you've done many good and many
bad things,
1000s
of things,
but one thing will be crucial to the next life, to the
very important mill. So it
's an incredibly important moment.
This seed will be 70, 80 years old. Home theater,
you'll be an animal, a
human,
a big nose or a small nose, an
American nose.
That's a very important moment, so
Williams says. It's very, very important, like
before, before they die.
Then he talks about what they did as very
good things and never argued with a
person,
never quarreled with such people, roamed
happily
and talked to them about all the good
things they did in the  What I did
after they died,
they still listen and they
watch. Now
talk to your family, do
you remember your father,
the good things he did? Yes, of course,
everyone remembers. In
2015, he helped this family,
he gave them a lot of money. But we
really had a good connection,
and your father, yes, yes.
And if the lottery number
is drawn at that moment,
then you help him, a good one found again,
and that is very, very
important.
The first seven weeks,
the first 29 days, that
is the day of death,
and even if they
died at 11:59 PM, that is still the
first day,
and then for seven days,
seven weeks, seven days,
canons, carefully
speaking about things,
only the good things, because he is
heard,
and that is very possible, that
the climate...
And now one last thing, and
then we go to bed.
We know how I... The friend,
the woman,
died 20 years ago, her daughter,
her daughter was only 20 years old then, so
very young.  Death
completely destroys lives.
When a parent dies, it's very
hard,
but when the child dies before the parents, there's
nothing worse.
Then I taught these things: for
seven weeks, speak well of
your daughter, about all the good things
she did.
I saw her recently,
and then I met Franck. That was
20 years ago.
I still talk to
my daughter every night in Munich during my
coffee meditation.
It's so beautiful, and we have such
a good relationship. I'm
very happy. I still talk to her.
So you don't have to stop after seven weeks,
and you can just
continue for
life. A boy with a beginning, and
he will be again.
That's also a reason to be with the family.
You always have to be together with the family
again. What has
been overcome is that it's temporary, that
a temporary separation. It's
not permanent. It's not forever.
That was also a reason to study. The majority, it's to
meet the family again.
You will be together in the same or paradise.
You will be very happy,
so you don't need to worry.
and speak with them, do
not quarrel with your relatives at this time of death
[Music]
[Applause]
the
preceding one from the
volunteer in Beijing will now the
mandala
like
[Music]
China
not so
sho well
[Music]
gea
beautiful
[Music]
b
then
[Music]
already